Guide to the Rice University Vietnamese Student Association records, 2004-2019 UA 372
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Vietnamese Student Association records
2004-2019
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 372
1.25 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
This collection consists of awards and scrapbooks from the Vietnamese Student Association.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Thu Nguyen donated materials in 2015.
Accruals
Additional materials are expected for this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of awards and scrapbooks from the Vietnamese Student Association.
Biographical / Historical
The Vietnamese Student Associaiton began around 1983. Their major events include the fall College Leadership Workshop and the spring Cultural Showcase.
Index Terms
Subjects
College students -- Texas; Universities and colleges
Places
Asian Americans
- Series I: Alphabetical Files
  - Awards, 2006, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Series II: Scrapbooks
  - 2004/2005 (Box 2)
  - 2009/2010 (Box 2)
- Series III: Memorabilia
  - College Leadership Workshop T-shirt, 2012 (Box 2)
  - College Leadership Workshop T-shirt, 2014 (Box 2)
  - College Leadership Workshop T-shirt (2), 2017 (Box 2)
  - College Leadership Workshop T-shirt (2), 2018 (Box 2)
  - College Leadership Workshop T-shirt, n.d. (Box 2)
  - College Leadership Workshop T-shirt, 2019 (Box 2)